Emanuel Javier Affatati

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

IT professional with more than 10 years of experience working in companies focused on SAP projects with a solid background in technical areas like development, architecture, analytics, security, and mobile technologies. On track to complete Salesforce Platform Developer I certification in 2022.



Winnipeg, MB R3M 0S6



(431) 668 - 1671



affatatiej@gmail.com



LinkedIn



Github

EDUCATION



Diploma, International Business Sep. 2021 – Aug. 2022



Master, Electronic Eng. - WES
March 2005 – Dec. 2011

SKILLS

- o HTML+JS+CSS
- o React
- o NodeJS
- o Python
- o Java
- o Abap
- o Apex

LANGUAGES

Fluent in English
Native in Spanish
Intermediate in French

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sr. Technology Consultant (Full-Stack developer)

SAP - Alumni

May 2013 - Sep. 2021

- Responsible for extending and building tailor-made web applications for customers from different industries.
- Built REST APIs and used Postman for testing and documentation.
- Developed detailed plans and accurate estimates for completion of build, system testing and implementation phases of projects.

Ssr. ABAP Consultant (Back-End developer) Capgemini

Apr. 2011 - May 2013

- Participated in the development and support of functionalities for different SAP Modules (FI – CO – SD – MM – PM – WM).
- Designed and coded different kinds of applications such as: reports, BADIs, User Exits, Workflow, interfaces and integrations between SAP and non-SAP systems.
- Performed technical unit testing on standard and developed objects.

CERTIFICATIONS

- o C FIORIADM 21 SAP Fiori System Administration
- o C FIORIDEV 20 SAP Fiori Application Developer
- o C TAW12 750 ABAP with SAP Netweaver 7.50
- o C CPI 13 SAP Integration Suite Developer
- o Microsoft Azure Fundamentals